hello everyone and welcome to my 4th season of GTNH
as usual the first thing we did before even starting the quest book is to rush into a place with a bed
that way we don't have to worry about the night
and now we can finally start doing the quests
so, as usual there are a bunch of annoying quests to do
and after quickly completing all of the easy quests
we got to the first quest where we can play it a little bit smarter
so we have to collect one stack of cobblestone
you could do that by just making an underground room which could be useful
but a better trick is to collect this cobblestone where it's in a way of something else
okay what I mean is that instead of randomly digging cobblestone, we can look for some ores
now if you didn't know
ores in this mod pack spawn in big veins
which are deposit every 3 by 3 chunks
okay to get a better view
you can hit F9 three times
if you hit F9 three times
you see those grids like that
at this point you should go in the middle of the 3 by 3 area
where there is this blue thing
and just dig there
now depending on how you play you either want
you either want to make a nice staircase
or some people just dig down
turn on keep inventory and teleport
back home once they need to go back
I still haven't decided how I'm going to play this season
think most likely I'm just going to enable keeping inventory at this point
here I found cassiterite sand
this is an ore
if you find an ore this is ore
it doesn't say small ore
I'm going to show small ore later
this one is a full ore
that means this spawn in a vein
and if you look up NEI, cassiterite sand
this one
now
sand
this one this is what we found
if you look it up there is this handy page
which tells you
veins stats: cassiterite sand and tin vein
now those veins spawn as huge clusters (of four?)
those can be almost 3 by 3 by 3 chunks big
every vein is a little bit different from the others
some are bigger, some are smaller, but they are all 9 blocks deep
the first three almost four layers of that huge deposit of ore is going to be composed of the primary ore
the bottom is going to be composed of the secondary and in between there is a lot of the between or two
then there is also this sporadic ore that is all around that huge chunks of ore
and there are a little bits ore of course here and there
usually there are like 1,000 of the primary ore in a vein
and there are like 100 of this sporadic one
that's more or less on every what vein is made out of
now here I dug another hole in the ground
and this time I found small graphite ore
now this is a small ore
so it's not a true vein but just a small ore
but it still is very important
because for example this is a small graphite ore
small graphite ore
to explain what I want to say
first let's look at small copper
so if you find a small copper ore
small copper ore, it has a page with small ore stats
small copper can spawn within 60 and 180 in the overworld
so if you find copper in the overworld at this height
it doesn't really mean anything
you can find copper anywhere in those planets in this range
and this is just a single ore that spawns like that to give you a little bit of copper
now copper is meaningless
but there are other ores that you have to get/you can only get in this way
so some small ores are really valuable
because that's the only way of getting something really specific
but it's mostly some rare gems
and some stuff in the late game
right now you don't really care about those small copper ores
but the thing is that if you look at these small graphite ore
small graphite or does not have small ore stats
but we found a small graphite ore even if it does not have a small stats page
that is because when a vein spawn, it doesn't spawn only the ore vein
it also spawns some small ores of that vein all above that vein
so for example graphite is part of the graphite
okay this is another graphite vein but
it does not spawn on the overworld
so we don't look at this
that means only
this vein can be part of it because overworld
so must be this one
this vein spawns only super deep
this one spawns only super deep
but we found a small ore
quite high in up
anyways what that means is that this is not a random ore that spawns anywhere
it can only spawn above graphite & diamond veins
and that means that below this ore we can find a lot of diamonds
and that's all that ore means
but you know we found diamonds
by the way I figure out you can right click on ore
for it to be added to the map
you don't have to break it
and after collecting enough stone
we can finally move on to the next tier
now this gear will require us to collect a lot of sand, gravel and clay
this stuff is required to make a smeltery
but the better tip is to just
just go find smeltery in a village
still, you have to collect all of the stuff required by those quests
but try not to use this stuff
I mean you're going to need this stuff
so feel free to use it
think it's easier to find a village with smeltery than doing this smeltery by hand at the first time
later on
clay too
later on you will need clay for so many many things
but there are way better workarounds for clay rather than looking for clay
we will see that later
for example you will need a lot of bricks
instead of making bricks from clay
it's way easier to use the brick house
I showed at the very beginning of this video
the next quest will ask us to make a bucket
I don't like using those items, those clay buckets
but I still think it's worth it to make multiples
so don't be afraid of wasting too much stuff
there's a thing called batch crafting
batch crafting means craft way more than you need
so you won't need it later on
it's something super important in GTNH
you should always craft extra
most of the times you should craft like 10 times what the quest asks you for
alright so I was saying trying to also calculate how much you need
to make a bucket you need 5 dusts
each dusts is made by 4 small dusts
which make from one clay
so you need a total of 20 clay balls for each bucket
so try to figure out the correct amount
also tools
make a lot of tools because you're going to eat through all of those tools really quickly
so don't craft one, craft a lot
now look at how quickly that's destroyed
many things I wanted to say
but next thing I want to say is
I hate those clay buckets
this playthrough and doing a bunch
(this playthrough?) only 6 probably I overdid it
I was saying sooner we will get iron buckets which are way better
there are a few downsides to those clay buckets
if you use those with lava I think they get destroyed
but right now that's the only thing we can do
there are probably ways of getting iron bucket right now
but let's follow the quest book
it's about I mean it's annoying to collect this clay
also earlier on
I said that there are better ways of getting clay
the way you should ideally use is
as soon as you can get a Steam Macerator
which should be one priority once you get to Steam Age
find a Montain made out terracotta and macerate it
it's going to be way faster and way more efficient than using a shovel to collect these (small?) amounts of clay
oh by the way, question rewards
my suggestion when you have to pick a choice is
you probably don't know
there are some points (where?) there are some really useful things you could choose from
but most of the time the choice
you can figure out what to choose, almost always probably
take this quest for an instance
the only big question will be the loot bags
personally I'm not a big fan of loot bags
most of these times you get trash out of those
just take whatever you think you like the most
I think for half of the quest, there is something I'd rather take than the loot bag
and half quest where there isn't anything interesting enough,
so just take the loot bag
and collecting 16 sand doesn't take that much effort
that's just food
may as well try your luck
you can get some useful stuff
okay we got food
if you look at the recipe for the loot bag
you can enchant it
getting a fortune three book in Stone Age is probably out of the question
that applies to other loot bags mostly
if you use the enchantment you get better loot
anyways if you look at the usages of the loot bag
you can see what you can actually get
and you can see the stats
for example in the Steam Age
Stone Age sorry
in the stone Age loot bag
you can basically get only foods
I mean, oh that would be nice actually I guess
collecting wood without a lumber axe is quite annoying
so that would be a thing
oh yeah one good thing about GT...
okay most people would hate it but
I like the progression where at the beginning you have a really trash axe
and later on you get the axe that can chop down a whole tree
I like that feeling of progression
you have to endure it at the beginning
but it feels rewarding once you can get the better axe
anyways what was I even doing
okay the next quest is going to make paper
the only reason I made more than one bucket is for this quest
because
if you do this thing with a single bucket
it's going to be a torture a nightmare
I started this YouTube channel
the reason I started this YouTube channel
was because there were people making videos
crying about having to do this stuff
so I started this YouTube channel just to show that
it's not that bad
maybe it's a little bit grindy
yeah it's probably a super grindy game
if you're into grindy games it's beautiful
if you are not
I don't know what to tell you
sorry
maybe GTNH is not for you
figure out yourself
we got the logs, we can make the wood pulp
oh wait you got (triple each?)
so technically I have enough requests
ah you know what
let's make more
let's batch craft
okay the thing is that
I want that 6 bucket because that way
we can't get the crafting station yet
so right now after you craft it
even if you leave the wood pulp in there
this crafting table doesn't
okay last version it will drop this on ground
now it keeps it in your inventory
cool
okay
another big thing which is not new of this version
but of the last one is that
we can do this
you can favorite a recipe
you can favorite our recipe
then you click as Ctrl+Shift+A on your favorite
and here you got this thing
then if you control scroll wheel
you can set a multiplier
then if you have all of the ingredients in your inventory
you have to press
shift + C
so nice
so craft more paper
oh that's so good
moving things in the crafting table is super annoying to me
some people may enjoy moving things in the crafting table
I do enjoy slowly collecting wood at the beginning
I mean after collecting
after collecting enough wood I get tired of it
I enjoy doing it at the beginning
like you can go listen to some podcast or
have something else play on the background
alright
Tinker's Construct is probably the most famous mod that is in modern Minecraft
but just in case if you don't know how those 4 works
first one is the stencil table
here you can decide
here you make basically those pattern things
those are parts of tools
for example I still don't have this one
you click you get this
if you have a pattern chest
this one is just a chest for those things
and if you put the next to this one
you can access the chest from this one without having to change UI
this is part builder which allows you to make
to actually make full parts
those are be forms here you craft things
once again this one can access your nearby chest
I think we're going to use (pink?) wood
not very sure probably quest book tells you what to do
what to use but
I'm guessing
so I think the quest book wants us to do
okay all of this
what does it want to do
okay pickaxe, shovel, flint axe
so you put here the thing the pattern
here the material
here you got the thing
and finally the tool station is the thing that allows you to actually make those tools
the tool station can also be used to repair those tools
you can repair it with the material of the pickaxe
and you can add some stuff to the tools to get some extra additions
there is this book which you can easily craft
but it was a reward
to craft it again
I got the (pt2?)
okay here it has you a little bit of things
and also it has you the modifier you can add
to get extra bonuses
but also, more simply if you look NEI anything like
bronze ingots
okay check the usages not the recipes
okay tool materials
here you can get the stats of those things
but most likely
there are also parts but okay I
think people already know how this mod works
I probably lost too much time
by the way I figured out you can right click on or
for it to be added to the map
you don't have to break it
also if you collect 270 blocks with your pickaxe
it will level up
and gain enough your ability to collect iron ore
but pure iron ore is not easy to find
rather, it's way easier to collect some of the iron oxides
this vein for example mineral sand
is something you can directly melt into iron
and very quickly you will realize that
in this mod pack, there are going to be a lot of different items
and inventory management becomes an issue
some people like to just throw everything in whatever chest they find
and then when they need something
they just use the T hotkey on NEI
and this will highlight the inventory that contain whatever you look for
but I'm not much of a fan
like I personally don't like this (approach?)
I mean it really works well to find whatever you need
but I don't like chests like this one
so what I usually do is
a little bit of inventory sorting
for example here I'm going to keep all of raw ores
crashed ores
dusts
this one is going to be random blocks
stones in block form
this one in dusts
this one is organic stuff
this one is actually un-sorted things
things I still have to decide where to put
this one is for coins
and those are the 3 most important
you will want next to your crafting station
later on this one will be upgrade to crafting station
and will be able to access this chest
which will be upgraded to
and here to keep I keep all of the tools
I'm considering the buckets as tools
I keep it like I like it
this chest is going to have all of the useful materials
so all of the things used into craftings basically
and this one is going to be for all of the machines
I mean those are not exactly machines right now
but you should get the idea
like you need this one to be smeltery
this one is tool station and craft table
so I call those machines later on the just for machines
now one cool trick
let's say you
went back from digging stuff
okay this trick I'm going to show
the first time you will have to do it manually but
let's say you have this trash in your inventory
if you click this arrow
it's going to look for nearby inventory that have this exact item inside it
and it will put this one where there already is
so for example here I have six
here I have to click this one
oh come on
it's a little bit glitch
yeah there is some configuration to make it work better
I think the range is too limited
there is only
yeah I don't know why doesn't check more containers
but you see the idea
it put the things into the correct chest
just click spam this button until it empties your inventory
I remember it's working a little
I remember it getting stuck a little bit sometimes
but usually it works
oh by the way
there are many different blocks you can use to build your house
there's a whole quest chapter
that is all about aesthetics blocks
it's not this one
okay this one completely overhauled
well there are many many many many blocks
most of those
(?) a little bit too early to look into those
but doesn't take much to unlock all of the various building blocks
usually, I wait for when I get the tinker hammer that can dig nine blocks at once
and then when I will go dig a lot of ore
I will come back with a lot of cobblestone
and I'm going to use the bricks for my house
so right now I'm going to keep it like that
and I will super carefully sleep as soon as it's night
and after some more grind
we managed to make our first multiblock
multiblock because it's a structured composed of multiple blocks
alright, you probably only want one of those
it's really useful for making better fuel
I heavily suggest using the creosote oil with a bucket in furnaces
each bucket of creosote oil should match 32 items
you get as much fuel on creosote as you get on charcoal
mostly you don't really have any other usage for the creosote oil at this tier
and you probably want this tank to always be empty
so may as well use these on furnace
but the thing I wanted to show is that with multiblocks
for every GregTech multiblock
always remember
most likely you will always want more than one
and to save on blocks you can wall share
wall share literally means
use one wall of the multiblock to make the second
so it just goes like that
and this way this one works
we save the nine blocks by building those like that
also they just added to the game a nice guide
which explains so many things
I'm not even reading this
because most likely 99 percent of those things are things I already know about
here you can see an example of a bigger wallshare
you can even make 8, you make 4 more on the back
then you can automate it
but right now we don't have access to the automation
so for the moment
it's only going to be useful for making some fuel
and after melting enough iron
we can finally move on to the next quests
and once again
don't make just one tool but prepare multiples
because you are going to need multiple of those tools
also when you make plates always make way more than you probably need them
and just get every tool
and with those new tools we unlock many*7 new things
now you should probably read each one of those quests
and try to understand what each of those items is
but I'm going to show you my favorite things out of all of those quests
so the first thing is going to be the new vending machine
where you can put in all of your coins
and then you can buy whatever you want
alright I think I'm too poor for any of those quests
so we will see this one again later
the next useful thing is the crafting station
this one is like a crafting table
but it can hold items when you close the UI
so you can leave things inside it
but most importantly
it can assess things in a nearby chest
that way you can leave all of your tools in the associated chest
and whenever you want to craft something
you can use the NEI, Auto Crafting
and it will automatically pull items from the chest
send it back
good
we can also make better storage
the gold chest have way bigger storage
and we can also make drawers
those can stack many stacks of items
ideally you want to use those for like cobblestone and such
but I'm going to do those a little bit later
because they do cost a little bit of wood
right now I don't have that many items to stock
so I will make this stuff later on when I will have more materials
so I can use the materials
and I will also need this space
right now I don't need this storage space
so I'm not going to use materials for this stuff
next we have this one the lunch box
this is quite cool because
it's just to manage food but I think it's super cool
now it has different mode
you can keep it open or closed
when it's closed and you click on a chest that has food
okay
when it's (indexed?) and you click on a chest with food
it takes the food from the chest
then you shift click
it closes
okay figure it out how it works
okay some point it takes food from the chest
and then you can eat it
there is a mode that allows you to edit its inventory
and a mode that you can just eat stuff inside it
that has enough space for a full food rotation
so you can't eat more than four times the same food in a row
this one helps you with that
but the thing that is probably most useful
if you don't have any luck
and the thing that I actually need now
is the ore finder
now if you cannot find some ore this one will help you
this one we need some Redstone
and to get the Redstone
the procedure is a little bit different from the other rules
basically you have to wash the impure Redstone
you have the crushed one you can crush it again
you got the impure dust
then you throw it in a cauldron and you got the clean dust
once you craft it
you're going to need some ore to put inside it
now you don't even need ore
you can put in this one anything that is made of what you want
I think (?) change the how it works
but yeah I'm not even too sure
I had really good luck with ores I think
I found basically everything
like I found two mica veins
one or two
but I found mica which is the rarest ore
we will need this way later on
but usually it's quite hard to find
I found a lot of diamond
anyways I did not find copper that's a weird thing
so we can take that small copper ore I found at the beginning of the stream
but did I leave it
think I didn't even collect that small copper
now wait I never found a copper ore
if you don't even have something to use in the wand
you can buy it in the vending machine
oh wait
there's a quest reward
okay
so I put this one in there
and now I'm basically going to walk around with this one in my hotbar
and it should start moving whenever I find that way
it should have like a 64 search depth
but most ores are above 64
so unless you go on a montain
it should work
and eventually after a lot of walking around
you should be able to find
whatever you're looking for
I mean make sure
you're looking for something that actually spawns in the dimension you're looking for
but eventually you should find it
and after looking for way longer than expected
finally found some copper ore
and I can't believe there wasn't a single copper vein
like I walked through all of that
can't believe that was the first copper vein I found
I was starting to lose hope but okay
you (might as well?) you find it
to make this one
okay look at the recipes
I don't know why it's showing this
anyways to make the ore finder wand
you basically need only iron, glod and Redstone
Iron is the most common ore
Gold and Redstone spawn as small ores a little bit everywhere
so this one should be really easy to get
those are really really easy to find
and once we have both tin and copper
we can get dust
we can get the dust out of those materials
and mix those to obtain bronze
and once we have enough bronze
we can finally craft our first small coal boiler
and with this
we are now in steam age
I think
are we?
are we not?
oh you have to do a check box
so as I was saying
and now I have to craft another
always make sure
you are following the quest
because now I have to craft another one of those for that reason
nice
so as I was saying
after we craft a second small coal boiler
we finally unlocked the steam age
and that is going to be what we will be doing in the next episode
bye bye
大家好，欢迎来到我的第四季GTNH
像往常一样，我们在开始任务书之前做的第一件事就是冲进一个有床的地方
这样我们就不用担心晚上了
现在我们终于可以开始做任务了
所以，像往常一样，有一堆烦人的任务要做
在快速完成所有简单的任务后
我们得到了第一个任务，我们可以玩得更聪明一点。
所以我们必须收集一堆鹅卵石
你可以做一个地下房间，这可能很有用。
但是更好的技巧是收集这块鹅卵石，它在其他地方。
好吧，我的意思是，我们可以寻找一些矿石，而不是随机挖掘鹅卵石
现在如果你不知道
这个mod包中的矿石在大静脉中产卵
每3乘3块存入一次。
好吧，为了获得更好的视野
你可以打三次F9
如果你按三次F9
你看那些网格是这样的
在这一点上，你应该去3乘3区域的中间
哪里有这个蓝色的东西
就在那里挖
现在取决于你怎么玩，你要么想要
你要么想做一个漂亮的楼梯
或者有些人只是往下挖
打开保持库存和传送
一旦他们需要回去就回家
我还没决定这个赛季要怎么打
我想最有可能的是，我现在要启用库存。
在这里我找到了锡石砂
这是矿石
如果你找到矿石，这就是矿石。
上面没说小矿石
我稍后要展示小矿石
这个是全矿石
这意味着这个产卵在静脉中
如果你查NEI，锡石砂
这个
现在
砂
这个这就是我们找到的
如果你查一下，有一个方便的页面。
这告诉你
矿脉统计：锡石砂和锡矿脉
现在这些静脉产卵为巨大的集群（四个？）
那些几乎可以是3乘3乘3的大块。
每根血管都和其他的有一点不同
有些大，有些小，但都有9个街区深
这一巨大矿床的前三层几乎四层将由原生矿石组成
底部将由次要部分组成，在两者之间有很多中间部分。
然后还有这种零星的矿石，就在那大块矿石周围
当然，这里和那里都有一点矿石。
通常一个矿脉里有1000块原生矿石
大概有100个这种零星的。
这或多或少是由静脉组成的
现在我又在地上挖了一个洞
这次我发现了小石墨矿
现在这是一个小矿石
所以这不是真正的矿脉，只是一个小矿石。
但它仍然非常重要
因为例如这是一个小石墨矿石
小石墨矿
来解释我想说的话
首先让我们看看小铜
所以如果你找到一个小铜矿
小铜矿，它有一个包含小矿石统计数据的页面
小铜可以在60和180内产卵
如果你在这么高的地方发现铜
这并不意味着什么
你可以在这个范围内的任何行星上找到铜
这只是一个单一的矿石，像这样产生，给你一点铜。
现在铜已经没有意义了
但是还有其他矿石你必须得到/你只能以这种方式得到
所以一些小矿石真的很值钱
因为这是得到真正具体的东西的唯一方法
但主要是一些稀有宝石
还有游戏后期的一些东西
现在你并不关心那些小铜矿
但问题是，如果你看看这些小石墨矿石
小石墨或没有小矿石统计数据
但我们发现了一个小石墨矿石，即使它没有小统计页面
这是因为当矿脉产卵时，它不仅产卵矿脉
它还在矿脉上方产生了矿脉中的一些小矿石
例如石墨是石墨的一部分
好吧这是另一个石墨静脉但是
它不会在世界上产卵
所以我们不看这个
这意味着只有
这条静脉可能是它的一部分，因为世界各地
一定是这个。
这条静脉只能超深产卵
这个只产卵超级深
但我们发现了一个小矿石
相当高的
不管怎样，这意味着这不是在任何地方产卵的随机矿石
它只能在石墨和钻石静脉上方产卵
这意味着在矿石下面我们可以找到很多钻石
这就是矿石的全部含义
但你知道我们找到了钻石
顺便说一句，我发现你可以右键单击矿石。
将其添加到地图中
你不必打破它
在收集到足够的石头后
我们终于可以进入下一层了
现在这个齿轮需要我们收集大量的沙子，砾石和粘土
这些东西是用来做冶炼厂的
但更好的建议是
去村子里找冶炼厂
尽管如此，你必须收集这些任务所需的所有东西
但尽量不要用这东西
我是说你会需要这些东西的
所以请随意使用它
认为找到一个有冶炼厂的村庄比第一次手工做这个冶炼厂更容易
后来
克莱也是
以后你会需要粘土做很多事情
但是有比寻找粘土更好的变通方法
我们稍后会看到
例如，您将需要大量砖块
而不是用粘土做砖
使用砖房要容易得多
我在这个视频的开头展示了
下一个任务会要求我们做一个桶
我不喜欢用那些东西那些泥桶
但我还是觉得赚倍数是值得的
所以不要害怕浪费太多东西
有一种东西叫做批量制作
批量制作意味着工艺比你需要的要多得多
所以你以后就不需要了
这是GTNH中非常重要的东西
你应该总是制作额外的
大多数时候，你应该制作10倍于任务要求的东西。
好吧，所以我说还要计算你需要多少。
做一个桶你需要5个灰尘
每个粉尘由4个小粉尘制成
由一种粘土制成
所以每个桶总共需要20个粘土球
所以试着弄清楚正确的数量
也是工具
制作很多工具，因为你会很快吃掉所有这些工具。
所以不要做一个，做很多
现在看看它被摧毁的速度有多快
很多我想说的话
但接下来我要说的是
我讨厌那些泥桶
这个游戏和做一堆
（这个播放？）只有6个，可能我做得太多了。
我是说早点我们会得到更好的铁桶。
那些泥桶有一些缺点
如果你把它们和熔岩一起使用，我想它们会被摧毁。
但现在这是我们唯一能做的
现在可能有办法得到铁桶。
但是让我们按照任务书
是关于我是说收集这种粘土很烦人
也早些时候
我说过有更好的方法来得到粘土
理想情况下应该使用的方式是
只要你能拿到蒸汽浓缩机
一旦你进入蒸汽时代，这应该是一个优先事项
找到一个用陶土做的山，然后浸泡它
这将比用铲子收集这些（小？）数量的粘土更快、更高效
哦对了问题奖励
当你必须做出选择时，我的建议是
你可能不知道
有一些点（在哪里？）有一些非常有用的东西你可以选择
但大多数时候选择
你可以想出该选择什么，几乎总是可能的
以这个任务为例
唯一的大问题是赃物袋
就我个人而言，我不太喜欢战利品袋。
大多数时候你从里面得到垃圾
随便拿你最喜欢的
我想在一半的探索中，我宁愿拿走一些东西，也不愿拿走战利品袋。
一半的探索，没有足够有趣的东西。
所以只要拿走赃物袋
收集16个沙子并不需要那么多精力
那只是食物
不妨试试你的运气
你可以得到一些有用的东西
好了我们有吃的了
如果你看看战利品袋的配方
你可以给它附魔
在石器时代获得财富三本书可能是不可能的
这主要适用于其他战利品袋
如果你使用结界，你会得到更好的战利品。
不管怎样，如果你看看战利品袋的用法
你可以看到你实际上能得到什么
你可以看到统计数据
例如在蒸汽时代
石器时代抱歉
在石头时代的战利品包里
你基本上只能得到食物
我是说，哦，我想那真的很好。
没有木材斧收集木材很烦人
所以那将是一件事
哦，是的，GT的一个好处是…
好吧，大多数人会讨厌它，但是
我喜欢这个过程，一开始你有一把非常垃圾的斧头。
之后你会得到可以砍倒一整棵树的斧头
我喜欢那种循序渐进的感觉
一开始你就得忍着
但是一旦你能得到更好的斧头，感觉就很有回报了。
不管怎样，我到底在做什么？
好的，下一个任务是做纸。
我做了不止一个桶的唯一原因就是为了这个任务
因为
如果你用一个桶做这件事
这将是一场折磨一场噩梦
我开了这个YouTube频道
我开始这个YouTube频道的原因
是因为有人在制作视频
为不得不做这些事而哭泣
所以我创建了这个YouTube频道只是为了表明
没那么糟啦
也许它有点磨人
是的，这可能是一场超级磨刀霍霍的比赛。
如果你喜欢格林迪游戏，那就太美了。
如果你不是
我不知道该怎么跟你说
抱歉
也许GTNH不适合你
弄清楚你自己
我们有原木可以做木浆
哦，等等，你有（三倍？）
所以从技术上讲，我有足够的要求。
啊你知道吗
让我们做更多
让我们批量制作
好吧问题是
我想要那个6桶，因为这样
我们还没拿到工艺品站
所以现在在你制作它之后
即使你把木浆留在里面
这张手工桌没有
好吧，最后一个版本，它会把这个掉在地上。
现在它把它保存在你的库存中
酷
好吧
这个版本的另一个大问题不是新的
但最后一个是
我们可以做到这一点
你可以喜欢一个食谱
你可以喜欢我们的食谱
然后你点击你最喜欢的Ctrl+Shift+A
这里有这个东西。
那么如果你控制滚轮
你可以设置一个乘数
那么如果你的库存里有所有的配料
你得按
Shift+C
真好
所以多做些纸
哦，那太好了。
在手工桌子上移动东西对我来说超级烦人
有些人可能喜欢在手工桌子上移动东西
一开始我很喜欢慢慢地收集木头
我是说收集之后
收集了足够的木材后，我厌倦了它
我喜欢一开始就做
比如你可以去听一些播客或者
让其他东西在背景上播放
好吧
修补匠的构造可能是现代Minecraft中最著名的mod
但以防万一，如果你不知道这4个是如何工作的
第一个是模板桌
在这里你可以决定
这里你基本上做了那些图案的东西。
那些是工具的一部分
例如，我仍然没有这个。
你点击你得到这个
如果你有一个图案的胸部
这个只是装那些东西的箱子
如果你把下一个放在这个旁边
您可以从这个箱子访问，而无需更改UI
这是零件生成器，可让您制作
真正制造完整的零件
这些是表格，你在这里制作东西。
再一次，这个可以进入你附近的胸部
我想我们要用（粉色？）木头
不太确定可能任务书告诉你该怎么做
用什么但是
我只是猜测
所以我想探索书想让我们做的是
好吧这一切
它想做什么
好吧镐铁锹火石斧
所以你把图案放在这里
这是材料
给你东西
最后，工具站是让你真正制作这些工具的东西
工具站也可以用来修理那些工具
你可以用镐的材料修理它
你可以在工具中添加一些东西来获得一些额外的添加。
有一本你可以轻松制作的书
但这是奖励
再次制作它
我得到了（pt2？）
好吧，这里有一些东西。
它也有你可以添加的修饰符。
获得额外奖金
但是，更简单的是，如果你看起来像NEI
青铜锭
好吧，检查用法而不是食谱
好吧工具材料
在这里你可以得到这些东西的统计数据
但最有可能的是
也有零件，但好吧，我
认为人们已经知道这个mod是如何工作的
我可能浪费了太多时间
顺便说一句，我发现你可以右键单击或
将其添加到地图中
你不必打破它
另外，如果你用镐收集270块
它会升级的
并获得足够的能力来收集铁矿石
但纯铁矿石不容易找到
相反，收集一些氧化铁要容易得多
例如矿砂
是可以直接融化成铁的东西
很快你就会意识到
在这个mod包中，会有很多不同的项目
库存管理成为一个问题
有些人喜欢把找到的东西都扔进箱子里
然后当他们需要什么的时候
他们只是在NEI上使用T热键
这将突出显示包含您要查找的任何内容的库存
但我不太喜欢
就像我个人不喜欢这样（方法？）
我是说找到你需要的东西真的很管用
但是我不喜欢这样的箱子。
所以我通常做的是
一点库存分类
例如，这里我将保留所有原始矿石
碎石
粉尘
这个将是随机块
块状石头
这个在尘土中
这个是有机的东西
这个实际上是未分类的东西
东西我还得决定放在哪里
这个是硬币用的
这是最重要的三个。
你会想要在你的工艺品站旁边
稍后这个将升级为制作站
并且能够进入这个箱子
将升级为
在这里，我保留了所有的工具
我把桶当成工具
我保持喜欢的样子
这个箱子里会有所有有用的材料
所以所有用于工艺品的东西基本上
这个将适用于所有机器
我的意思是，现在这些还不完全是机器。
但你应该明白
就像你需要这个来冶炼一样
这个是工具站和工艺桌
所以我稍后将这些机器称为机器专用
现在一个很酷的技巧
比如说你
从挖东西回来
好吧我要展示的这个技巧
第一次你必须手动完成，但是
假设你的库存中有这些垃圾
如果你点击这个箭头
它会寻找附近有这个确切物品的库存。
它会把这个放在已经有的地方。
例如，这里我有六个。
在这里，我必须点击这个。
哦得了吧
有点小故障
是的，有一些配置可以让它更好地工作。
我觉得范围太有限了
只有
是的，我不知道为什么不检查更多的容器。
但你看到了这个想法
它把东西放在正确的箱子里
只需单击垃圾邮件此按钮，直到它清空您的库存
我记得有点效果
我记得有时候会卡住一点
但通常它是有效的
哦对了
有许多不同的块您可以用来建立您的房子
有一整章的任务
这就是美学块
不是这个
好吧，这个完全检修过了。
嗯，有很多很多很多的街区。
大多数那些
（？）现在调查这些还为时过早
但解锁所有不同的积木并不需要太多
通常我会等着拿到能同时挖九个街区的修补匠锤
然后我什么时候去挖很多矿石
我会带着很多鹅卵石回来
我要用砖头建造我的房子。
所以现在我要保持这样
一到晚上，我会非常小心地睡觉。
经过更多的磨练
我们设法制作了我们的第一个多块
多块，因为它是由多个块组成的结构化
好吧，你可能只想要其中一个。
它对制造更好的燃料非常有用
我强烈建议在炉子里用桶来装杂酚油
每桶杂酚油应匹配32件物品
木炭和杂酚油能提供同样多的燃料
这层的杂酚油基本上没有其他用途
你可能希望这个水箱永远是空的
所以不妨在炉子上使用这些
但我想展示的是多块
对于每个GregTech多块
永远记住
很可能你总是想要不止一个。
为了节省积木，你可以分享墙壁。
墙分享字面意思是
用多块的一面墙做第二块
所以就这样了
这样这个就可以了。
这样的建筑可以拯救9个街区
他们还在游戏中添加了一个不错的指南
这解释了很多事情
我都没在读这个
因为很有可能99%的事情都是我已经知道的。
在这里你可以看到一个更大的墙分享的例子
你甚至可以做8个，你在背面再做4个。
然后你可以自动化它
但现在我们无法访问自动化
所以目前
它只对制造燃料有用
在融化足够的铁之后
我们终于可以继续下一个任务了
再一次
不要只做一个工具，而是准备倍数
因为您将需要多种工具
另外，当你制作盘子时，总是比你可能需要的要多得多。
并获得所有工具
使用这些新工具，我们可以解锁许多*7新事物
现在你可能应该阅读这些任务中的每一个
并尝试了解这些项目中的每一个是什么
但我将向你们展示在所有这些任务中我最喜欢的东西。
所以第一件事就是新的自动售货机。
您可以放入所有硬币的地方
然后你可以买任何你想要的东西。
好吧，我想我太穷了，无法完成这些任务。
所以我们稍后会再次看到这个。
下一个有用的东西是制作站
这个就像一张手工桌
但它可以在您关闭UI时保存项目
所以你可以把东西留在里面
但最重要的是
它可以评估附近箱子里的东西
这样你就可以把所有的工具都放在相关的箱子里
无论何时你想制作一些东西
您可以使用NEI，汽车工艺
它会自动从箱子里取出物品。
寄回去
好
我们还可以做更好的存储
金色的箱子有更大的储物空间。
我们还可以做抽屉。
那些可以堆叠很多堆叠的物品
理想情况下，您想将这些用于鹅卵石等
但是我稍后会再做这些。
因为它们确实需要一点木头。
现在我没有那么多商品要库存。
所以我稍后会做这些东西，当我有更多的材料时。
这样我就可以使用这些材料了
我也需要这个空间。
现在我不需要这个储物空间
所以我不会用这些材料。
接下来我们有这个饭盒。
这很酷，因为
只是为了管理食物但我觉得超级酷
现在它有不同的模式
你可以保持它打开或关闭
当它关闭时，你点击一个有食物的箱子
好吧
当它（索引？）你点击一个有食物的箱子
它把食物从箱子里拿出来
然后你移动点击
它关闭了
好吧弄清楚它是如何工作的
好吧，在某种程度上，它从胸部获取食物
然后你就可以吃了
有一种模式允许您编辑其库存
还有一种模式，你可以吃里面的东西。
有足够的空间进行完整的食物轮换
所以你不能连续吃超过四倍相同的食物
这个可以帮你
但最有用的可能是
如果你运气不好
我现在真正需要的是
是矿石发现者
现在如果你找不到一些矿石，这个会帮你的。
这个我们需要一些红石
并获得红石
程序与其他规则有点不同
基本上你必须洗不纯的红石
你有压碎的那个，你可以再压碎一次。
你得到了不纯的灰尘
然后你把它扔进大锅，你就得到了干净的灰尘
一旦你制作它
你需要一些矿石放在里面
现在你甚至不需要矿石了
你可以在这个里面放任何你想要的东西。
我认为（？）改变它的工作方式
但是是的我甚至不太确定
我想我在矿石方面运气很好。
我基本上什么都找到了
就像我发现了两条云母静脉
一两个
但我发现云母是最稀有的矿石
我们稍后会需要这种方式
但通常很难找到。
我发现了很多钻石
不管怎样，我没有找到铜，这很奇怪。
所以我们可以把我在溪流开始时发现的小铜矿
但我离开了吗？
我想我甚至没有收集那个小铜。
等等，我从来没有找到过铜矿石。
如果你连魔杖里可以用的东西都没有
你可以在自动售货机里买到
哦等等
有任务奖励
好吧
所以我把这个放在那里。
现在我基本上要带着这个在我的热酒吧里走来走去
只要我找到那条路，它就应该开始移动。
它应该有64个搜索深度
但大多数矿石都在64以上
所以除非你去山上
它应该有效
最终在四处走动之后
你应该能找到
不管你在找什么
我是说确保
你要找的东西会在你要找的维度中产生
但最终你会找到它
在寻找比预期更长的时间之后
终于找到了一些铜矿
我不敢相信没有一条铜矿脉
就像我经历了这一切
真不敢相信这是我发现的第一条铜脉
我开始失去希望了，但没关系。
你（也可以？）你找到了
做这个
好吧看看食谱
我不知道为什么会显示这个。
无论如何要制作探矿棒
你基本上只需要铁、金和红石
铁是最常见的矿石
黄金和红石到处都是小矿石
所以这个应该很容易买到。
那些真的很容易找到
一旦我们有了锡和铜
我们可以得到灰尘
我们可以把这些材料上的灰尘清除掉
并将它们混合以获得青铜
一旦我们有了足够的青铜
我们终于可以制造出第一台小型燃煤锅炉了
有了这个
我们现在处于蒸汽时代
我觉得
是吗？
我们不是吗？
哦，你必须做一个复选框
正如我所说
现在我必须制作另一个
始终确保
你在追求
因为现在我必须为此制作另一个。
很好
正如我所说
在我们制造出第二台小型燃煤锅炉后
我们终于解锁了蒸汽时代
这将是我们下一集要做的
拜拜